<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Choria Stream Replicator</title><link>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/index.html</link><description>Recent content on Choria Stream Replicator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/installation/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/installation/index.html</guid><description>We distribute an RPM or Docker container for the Stream Replicator package. Debian is not supported at present.
YUM Repository For RPMs we publish releases but also nightly builds to our repositories.
Users of our Puppet modules will already have these repositories available.
Release [choria_release] name=Choria Orchestrator Releases mirrorlist=http://mirrorlists.choria.io/yum/release/el/$releasever/$basearch.txt enabled=True gpgcheck=True repo_gpgcheck=True gpgkey=https://choria.io/RELEASE-GPG-KEY metadata_expire=300 sslcacert=/etc/pki/tls/certs/ca-bundle.crt sslverify=True Nightly Nightly releases are named and versioned stream-replicator-0.99.0.20221109-1.el7.x86_64.rpm where the last part of the version is the date.</description></item><item><title>Configuration</title><link>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/configuration/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/configuration/index.html</guid><description>Configuring the Replicator requires having credentials and stream details for both the Source and Target streams.
If you just want to duplicate/combine streams in the same NATS Server Cluster you should probably use a JetStream Source which Choria Broker also supports.
Review the sub-sections for scenario specific details.</description></item><item><title>Monitoring</title><link>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/monitoring/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://choria-io.github.io/stream-replicator/monitoring/index.html</guid><description>Message Source Information Every message that gets copied has a header added called Choria-SR-Source with an example being CHORIA_REGISTRATION 10631 US-EAST-1 PARTITION1 1673433286805. Using this you can determine where any copied message is from, which worker copied it and the delay between the message creation, and it&amp;rsquo;s arriving in the target.
From this we know the following:
The source stream is called CHORIA_REGISTRATION The message we are looking at has a Stream Sequence of 10631 in the source stream The replicator name (configured using top level name in the config file) is US-EAST-1 The name set on the stream configuration is PARTITION1 this allows you to tell which specific copier config copied it, helping to identify ordering or partition logic issues The message was stored in the source at 1673433286805 which is a milliseconds since Unix epoch.</description></item></channel></rss>